# 大家好 今天天氣比較好哦
Hi everyone! The weather is better today.
# 我把那個狗崽子
I'll take the small puppies,
# 捉出來 曬一下太陽
take them out here to have a sunbath.
# 都沒曬過太陽
It's their first time.
# 哎喲 知道我來啦 一邊叫我到啦
Ayo! They know I'm coming. They're calling me.
# 哇 那麼兇
Wa! You're so fierce!
# 那麼大條
So big
# 小狗
Puppies
# 小黑 小黑 你湊甚麼熱鬧哇
Blacky! Blacky! Why are you tagging along?
# 走開走開走開
Go 'way, go 'way, go 'way!
# 哎喲 這 小看
Ayo! This one, look!
# 你看這小狗
Look at this puppy.
# 跟它 它 差不多大啦
They, they're al...almost the same size.
# 這個 胖嘟嘟的
This one is, chubby chubby,
# 圓嘟嘟的
round and plumpy.
# 來 你看
C'mon! Look!
# 看看
Have a look!
# 給大家看一看
Show them to the audience!
# 不怕 我在這裡 誰敢欺負他們
No worries! Who would dare to bully them when I'm around?
# 來
C'mon!
# 小狗
Puppies!
# 你看
Look!
# 先曬一下太陽 舒服多了吧 你看
Have a sunbath first. Does it feel good? Look!
# 這個就是最會享受的
This one loves sunshine the most.
# 四腳朝著天來曬
It has the sunbath lying on its back.
# 哦是不是
Oh! Don't you?
# 好爽吧
It's great, eh?
# 是不是
Isn't it?
# 你看 這個就
Look! And this one...
# 幹嘛
What happened?
# 動來動去
You're so restless.
# 你看 它會爬啦
Look! It's crawling.
# 它這個腳趾甲好利呀
It's toenails are really sharp.
# 好 你不要叫 你不要叫
Alright! Don't yelp! Don't yelp!
# 肥嘟嘟的
Chubby, chubby
# 4條狗都好肥呀
All four puppies are so fat.
# 不過 4條狗跟 跟有點
But all four puppies are like, are a bit,
# 都不像狗媽媽
they don't look like their mom.
# 從小耳朵 不像
No, they don't. From the small ears...
# 太胖啦 它們耳朵都掉下去啦
They're so fat, that they even have floppy ears.
# 你看 狗媽媽想把它們拉回去
Look! Their mom wants to pull them back.
# 不要緊 不要緊
It's alright! It's alright!
# 張開嘴
Open you mouth.
# 這裡 你看 狗媽媽想把它們叼回去啦
Here, look! Their mom wants to take them back.
# 好 好 好偉大的媽媽呀
Wh, wha, what a great mom!
# 等一下我幫你抱回去
I'll take them back for you in a while.
# 你叼不走的 叼得它呱呱叫
You can't take them. They would scream and scream and scream.
# 我來
Let me do it.
I say let me do it.
# 狗媽媽不肯
She's not letting me.
# 我們把它抱回去啦
Let's take them back.
# 我幫你抱回去
I'm taking them back for you.
# 誒 4條
Ay! Four puppies
# 不讓你咬
Don't use your mouth.
# 你肯定餓啦
You must be very hungry,
# 想吃奶啦
so you want milk.
# 好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.